-
Oh, my God.
What shall I do?
Hi, I'm Sakura Endo and I'm in a place called Kakunodate in Akita Prefecture.
Yes, I've been doing some research, and the town is really beautiful, so I decided to come here.
So I decided to come here!
So I'd like to go for a walk. I'm off!
Wow, it's a little cool!
This is my first time in Akita!
First time here!
I wanted to see the samurai residences.
It's about a 10-15 minute walk to get there.
Hey.
Hey...
Hey, I really can't talk.
I don't talk much to begin with.
If I don't do it regularly, I'll forget.
It's so quiet.
Wow.
It's so quiet, I could do a wow.
I can wow.
I could do that.
What am I saying?
I mean, there's no one here.
There's doggy doggy.
You scared the shit out of me.
It's big.
There's a dog.
You scared me a little bit.
Do you know, I'm not very good with animals.
I'm a little scared of them.
I think I've gotten over it recently.
But I'm still a little scared of them, so I run away.
Cats, dogs...
I run away when they come close to me.
They're cute, though.
Oh, even the barber shop is open.
I made eye contact with an old man.
I made eye contact with Grandpa, the barber.
I made eye contact with grandpa.
He said, "Come here.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Excuse me, excuse me
Hello, how are you?
I'm from Tokyo.
I'm from Tokyo. I just came to visit.
What kind of entertainer are you?
I'm an idol. Nogizaka46.
That's great.
Not at all.
I saw you outside earlier.
So...
I was wondering if I could talk to you for a minute.
Oh, yeah, yeah, sure.
Really? I'm glad.
Nogizaka40X?
Yes, sir.
Let's take a picture, shall we?
Oh, a picture?
Yes, sir.
Okay. I'm glad you took my picture.
Well, I'm going to go for a walk.
Have a good time.
Okay. Thank you very much.
Okay, good luck.
All right. All right.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
I'm nervous.
I'm so glad you could make the exchange.
I don't know, I'm glad.
I wish we could have gotten to know each other better.
I'm not very charming in my own little way.
It was nice to meet you.
Ah! Buke Yashiki.
They said 6 more minutes!
Wow!
Here's a picture of the Buke Yashiki Street.
I think we're almost there.
When you turn there...
I have a feeling it's going to be there.
Oh no...
People are running away.
Oh, wow, isn't this the place?
Wow.
Oh, this is it.
There you go.
You can't see my face at all!
It's like this.
It goes on and on.
I'm going to walk here.
I'm off!
I wonder if the leaves will turn red in the fall.
Sorry, the angle is from the bottom.
It's so green!
It's amazing!
I found a general store!
Do we have to get a permit?
All right. - All right.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm filming for YouTube right now, and I was wondering if there's any way we could film inside?
Or a cameraman?
Okay. - Okay.
Yes, sir.
Great.
I'm just going to go in here for a minute.
It was nice inside, and I'd like to see some souvenirs and stuff.
Excuse me.
He's so cute.
Good night.
Cherry blossom pool.
Amazing!
Iburi goko (smoked salmon roe) for sale.
Curitampo
Iburi goko (pickled smoked daikon pickles)
Looks delicious!
A congratulatory gift... but handing out koban would be nice too
Koban or congratulatory gift, I'm not sure.
I think both visuals are cute.
Too cute!
I bought some souvenirs. There's my favorite messenger, so I think I'll do it and go home.
This!!!
I'll be happy no matter what I get.
Ah, it's too dark to see.
Kiritampo!
I'm saying fate.
I'm so happy.
I've got a kiritampo.
Turnip.
I didn't know it was you.
Thank God no one's here.
I got a good deal. - Good.
We'll just have to keep walking.
Oh, my God.
Is that Aoyagi House?
Wow.
What?
It says here that this is a representative samurai residence of the Tateno area.
Hello.
I'm looking for you.
Huh?
huh?
That's great.
Excuse me.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
I can't stop staring at it.
Can you lift this?
Can I lift it? Here.
Take this one.
Can we hold it?
Can I hold this precious thing?
Excuse me.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Let's get it out.
It's heavy.
I've got it.
Let's take it apart.
This is too interesting.
He said it's a picture of the human body, down to the smallest detail.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's amazing!
That's a lot of work.
This is how they used to put out fires.
The face...
We'll have to go when no one's around.
There's no one there right now.
Who would you like to see?
Samurai
Akita Obako
Akita
This is the one after all.
Good night.
No one's here, right?
Nobody's here, right?
I'm a little embarrassed.
I hope you're getting this.
Yeah, I think so.
Thank you very much.
I've just been in a samurai residence.
I've been enjoying it.
Well...
Yesterday...
I'm going to Akita Prefecture.
After we decided to go to Akita...
I actually wanted to thank Mr. Himura
I wanted to thank you.
I was asking him if he had any recommendations.
Actually, he told me.
I'm so glad. I had no choice but to go with your recommendation.
This is the place, isn't it?
Hello.
Hello... is it okay if we come in for the photo shoot?
I'm so glad you came.
Let's see, let's see...
One miso kiritampo and...
Konnyaku? This is konnyaku and daikon radish.
Daikon? Daikon radish.
Fried radish, please. And a little bit of this.
I'll get my hair done.
It's nice and quiet.
So calm.
They're all nice.
The shopkeepers here...
And the shopkeeper who brought me some souvenirs.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Some kiritanpo!
Ito konjac. Chikara konjac.
Oden
Tea
Good.
Then I'll have some. Bon appétit.
Let's start with the tea.
It's warm.
Where do we start? Kiritanpo first?
Where shall we start?
What shall we eat first?
Kiritanpo, after all?
It smells so good!
It's the first time to eat kiritanpo.
Bon appétit.
Delicious!
Ah! Delicious~!
So delicious!
It is daikon (Japanese radish) in oden. Daikon is my favorite among oden.
Bon appétit.
Mmm!
Warm.
Delicious.
The mustard.
I heard it's pretty spicy.
Should I dip it in?
I'm not sure.
I'm not sure if I want to try it with mustard.
Let's put some on.
Yeah. - Spicy!
Hot! Umami!
Yum!
The mustard one is a little more...
Um... Hot!
Daikon radish is so good!
Yum!
I'm so happy!
Spicy!
I put a little too much on.
Maybe a little too much.
Yeah, it's okay.
Thank you for the food.
I finished it.
It was delicious.
I'm so full!
The mustard was so good.
It's all delicious
I'm full.
Let's go for a walk
Thank you for the food.
Delicious.
Five, four, three.
Is it okay?
I think I'm missing something.
Oh, it looks good, doesn't it? I flew as hard as I could.
Mission accomplished.
I've been walking from the samurai residence for a while.
Shinmeisha Shrine.
I was hoping to pay my respects here.
I'm hoping to get a red seal.
I can see the torii gate soon
Here we are
Here I go!
Nogizaka46 will be releasing their 37th single on December 11th.
This single will be our last single in December.
I hope we can all work together again to create something great.
I'm going to pay my respects at this shrine.
I'm going to pray for a hit first!
Climbing the stairs reminds me of praying for a hit in Monoprix.
You climbed with Kakki.
Okay...
Let's pay our respects.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Oh, wow.
Prayer's done.
I said, "Let's get a hit.
All right, let's go get your husband.
Let's wrap up the trip.
October's master
Can you write down "October's Master"?
Yes, that's right.
Kakuno Date in Akita
We've just finished our stroll through the samurai residences of Kakuno Date in Akita Prefecture.
I paid my last visit to a shrine and got a red seal.
I feel so refreshed afterwards.
I'm crying a lot!
Now we're ready for December.
I'll be able to work hard again for the release of the new song in December.
Thank you for your continued support!
And thank you for watching Sakusanpo. Please subscribe to our channel and give us a high rating!
Bye bye!
Thank you for watching!